

Mateusz Fonfara

Full Stack Developer

My passion is creating tools for other people to make their life easier. I have experience with each stage of creating applications, from its concept, by the design and architecture planning to final execution and deployment.

I run a blog on medium.com where I share my thoughts on the IT world and contribute to open source.

CONTACT

mateusz.fonfara96@gmail.com

github.com/Matii96

matii96.github.io

SKILLS

- Node.js / Nest.js
- Python
- Vue.is
- Angular
- C# / .net
- PostgreSQL / MySQL
- Software Architecture

LANGUAGES

English B2 (FCE exam)

INTERESTS

- History
- Swimming

WORK HISTORY

Back-end developer, Tech lead 2021-08 -Current

Netguru, Poland - Poznań

 Consulting & leading the team of top notch experts through a transformation of e-commerce platform for major fast deliveries company

Software Architect, Full Stack Developer 2018-06 -2021-07 ITM Software House, Poland - Olsztyn

- Applied established development methodologies such as microservices and event sourcing to architecture
- Designed unified authorization system for all web and mobile applications

Back End Developer 2018-02 -2018-06 NETTOM, Poland, - Olsztyn

- Built databases and table structures for web applications.
- Used php symfony to build projects.

EDUCATION

Master of Science: Information Technology 2019-02 -2021-03 University of Warmia And Mazury - Olsztyn

◆ Thesis: Soldier support system

2018-02 - Bachelor of Science: Information Technology 2018-06 University of Warmia And Mazury - Olsztyn

Thesis: Chatbot - virtual guide

- Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w celu rekrutacji zgodnie z art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a Rozporządzenia Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (ogólne rozporządzenie o ochronie danych).
- I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).